const dummyData = {"Math":[{"subject":"Math","question":"This is demo question ","hint":"Answer all questioins","options":[{"option":"one","selected":false,"correct":true},{"option":"deux","selected":false,"correct":false}]},{"subject":"Math","question":"This is demo question 2","hint":"Answer all questioins","options":[{"option":"one","selected":false,"correct":false},{"option":"deux","selected":false,"correct":true}]},{"subject":"Math","question":"This is demo question 3","hint":"Answer all questioins","options":[{"option":"one","selected":false,"correct":false},{"option":"deux","selected":false,"correct":true}]}],"Chemistry":[{"subject":"Chemistry","question":"This is a demo question 1","hint":"Answer all questions","options":[{"option":"one","selected":false,"correct":true},{"option":"deux","selected":false,"correct":false},{"option":"three","selected":false,"correct":false}]},{"subject":"Chemistry","question":"This is a demo question 2","hint":"Answer all questions","options":[{"option":"one","selected":false,"correct":true},{"option":"deux","selected":false,"correct":false},{"option":"three","selected":false,"correct":false}]},{"subject":"Chemistry","question":"This is a demo question 4","hint":"Answer all questions","options":[{"option":"one","selected":false,"correct":true},{"option":"deux","selected":false,"correct":false},{"option":"three","selected":false,"correct":false}]},{"subject":"Chemistry","question":"This is a demo question 5","hint":"Answer all questions","options":[{"option":"one","selected":false,"correct":true},{"option":"deux","selected":false,"correct":false},{"option":"three","selected":false,"correct":false},{"option":"4","selected":false,"correct":false}]}],"Biology":[{"subject":"Biology","question":"This is a demo question 1","hint":"Answer all questions","options":[{"option":"one","selected":false,"correct":true},{"option":"deux","selected":false,"correct":false},{"option":"three","selected":false,"correct":false}]},{"subject":"Biology","question":"This is a demo question 3","hint":"Answer all questions","options":[{"option":"one","selected":false,"correct":true},{"option":"deux","selected":false,"correct":false},{"option":"three","selected":false,"correct":false}]},{"subject":"Biology","question":"This is a demo question 2","hint":"Answer all questions","options":[{"option":"one","selected":false,"correct":true},{"option":"deux","selected":false,"correct":false}]},{"subject":"Biology","question":"This is a demo question 4","hint":"Answer all questions","options":[{"option":"one","selected":false,"correct":true},{"option":"deux","selected":false,"correct":false},{"option":"three","selected":false,"correct":false},{"option":"you","selected":false,"correct":false}]},{"subject":"Biology","question":"This is a demo question 6","hint":"Answer all questions","options":[{"option":"one","selected":false,"correct":true},{"option":"deux","selected":false,"correct":false},{"option":"three","selected":false,"correct":false}]}],"Computer Science":[{"subject":"Computer Science","question":"What is computer science 1","hint":"Answer all questions number one is compulsory","options":[{"option":"Option1","selected":false,"correct":true},{"option":"Option2","selected":false,"correct":false},{"option":"Option3","selected":false,"correct":false},{"option":"Option4","selected":false,"correct":false},{"option":"Option5","selected":false,"correct":false}]},{"subject":"Computer Science","question":"What is computer science 2","hint":"Answer all questions number one is compulsory","options":[{"option":"Option1","selected":false,"correct":true},{"option":"Option2","selected":false,"correct":false},{"option":"Option3","selected":false,"correct":false}]},{"subject":"Computer Science","question":"What is computer science 3","hint":"Answer all questions number one is compulsory","options":[{"option":"Option1","selected":false,"correct":true},{"option":"Option2","selected":false,"correct":false},{"option":"Option3","selected":false,"correct":false},{"option":"Option4","selected":false,"correct":false}]},{"subject":"Computer Science","question":"What is computer science 4","hint":"Answer all questions number one is compulsory","options":[{"option":"Option1","selected":false,"correct":true},{"option":"Option2","selected":false,"correct":false},{"option":"Option3","selected":false,"correct":false},{"option":"Option4","selected":false,"correct":false}]}]}

export default dummyData;